所以你的计划是什么, Dean?
So what's your plan,Dean?
我的意思是, 在你实习结束后?
I mean,after your internship?
我完成学业.
I finish school.
完成学业后, 我寻找一份工作.
After school,I look for a job.
以你的资历,
With your qualifications,
你不会有什么大问题的.
you won't have much of a problem.
我希望那是真的.
I wish that were true.
很多有资格的人找不到工作.
Lots of qualified people can't get work.
因为企业雇不起人吗?
Because businesses can't afford to hire people?
那是他们所说的.
That's what they say.
尤其带上福利.
Especially with benefits.
所以我可能不会得到一份工作  很长一段时间里.
So I may not get a job for a long time.
如果我不能得到一份工作.
And if I can't get a job,
失业率必定是过高了.
unemployment must be too high.
当然, 我仍然必须还清我的学生贷款.
Of course,I still have to pay off my student loans.
你必须自己支付大学的费用吗?
You have to pay for university yourself?
政府不给你补贴吗?
Doesn't the government subsidize you?
不多. 你大多得靠自己.
Not much.You're pretty much on your own.
多有趣啊 报纸头条开始影响你的生活了.
Funny how the newspaper headlines start to affect your life.
失业, 通货膨胀...
Unemployment,inflation....
Well 那不是很令人愉快, 是吗?
Well that's not very cheerful,is it?
要是体育版更好一些该多好!
If only the sports pages were better!